infochimps.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Infochimps

## INFOCHIMPS.COM PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy is posted to inform our users such as you (“you” or “user”) of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of the Service. Infochimps reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason without notice to you. As a best practice, Infochimps recommends that all users visit this page regularly to monitor any changes. Your use of the Service is governed by the Terms of Service (“TOS”) available at http://www.infochimps.com/terms, and your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to and acceptance of this Privacy Policy, the TOS, and any future changes.

By using the Service, you are agreeing to our collection and processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and any future iterations. Any questions, concerns or comments you have about our use of your personally identifiable information or this policy may be directed to us at [help@infochimps.com](mailto:help@infochimps.com).

## A Note About the Privacy of Children Under 13

The Service is not directed to or otherwise promoted for use by children under the age of thirteen (13). Infochimps does not knowingly collect or use any personal information of users of the Service who are under the age of thirteen (13).

## The Information We Collect

Users can access limited features of the Service without disclosing personal information. In order to access other portions or features of the Service, users must register for an account, which will provide the registrant with additional access to the Service. During the account registration process, Infochimps will collect some personally identifiable information, including but not limited to: IP Address, user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number and any and all other information that you share with us.

We receive and store any information you enter through the Service or give us in any other way. You should be aware that portions of the Service contain functions for collecting and tracking non-personally identifiable information about you including your IP address, domain name, pages that were viewed, where you were referred from, and technical information such as browser type and operating system. If you have volunteered personal information, then Infochimps may associate such information with information already tracked, as well as track additional personal information.

## Why We Collect this Information

The information Infochimps collects from you is used to respond to your request for products and services, for provision of such products and services, to determine your satisfaction with your purchase(s) and to customize our future interactions to meet your needs. The information about your computer and/or your mobile device is used to analyze marketing statistics, identify trends and continually improve the way in which Infochimps serves you.

## Contact Information, Storage and Sharing

Except as provided herein, Infochimps will not sell or give any of the information Infochimps collects through the Service or through any personal correspondence to a third-party entity. Infochimps reserves the right to use that information, however, to market any additional services and products to you. Infochimps sometimes hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as sending newsletters, providing customer service, and performing statistical analysis of our services. Infochimps will only provide those companies with the information that they need to provide us with such services, and Infochimps will prohibit them from using that information for any other purpose. You will always have the right to opt out of this type of communication by following the unsubscribe instructions included in any of the marketing emails Infochimps sends you. Infochimps may store and process in the United States or any other country in which Infochimps, Inc. or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents maintain facilities. By using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

## Use of User Information

Infochimps reserves the right to compile, save, use within the scope of Infochimps’ activities, and analyze any and all user data (registration data, use history, etc.). Infochimps intends to use personally-identifiable user data solely for internal purposes only, including without limitation for the purposes of responding to your requests for information and for contacting you. Infochimps may use information about our users on an aggregated basis and will often share such data with unaffiliated third parties. An “unaffiliated” third party means one that (i) is not controlled by Infochimps, (ii) does not control Infochimps, and (iii) is not controlled by the same party controlling Infochimps. For example, Infochimps may hire other companies to handle the processing of payments, to provide data storage, to host websites, to fulfill orders and shipments, to assist in marketing, to conduct audits, etc. After Infochimps or any third party acting on our behalf discloses your personal information to an “unaffiliated” third party in such instances, Infochimps can no longer control the use or further disclosure of your personal information. Consequently, Infochimps and any third party acting on our behalf will not be responsible to you for such use or further disclosure.

## IP Address Use

When you log in to the Service Infochimps will collect your browser type and IP address. Infochimps may also store some information about your browser using “cookies”. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Infochimps uses session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in; however, you have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to set your computer to accept cookies from the Service, you may also choose to be logged into the Service automatically. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Service or the other websites that you visit and you may experience technical problems receiving current information from such cookie-disabled websites or services.

## Law and Law Enforcement Compliance

Infochimps will cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. This includes the disclosure, without notice, of any information Infochimps has collected about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as Infochimps, at its sole discretion, believes necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Infochimps or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

## Security

Infochimps is very concerned and sensitive to the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. Infochimps uses various security measures to both protect the Service and keep your information as safe as possible. Infochimps secures the e-mail address you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Infochimps strives to protect your personal information, Infochimps cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Should a breach of security occur, Infochimps will make any legally required disclosures of the breach as soon as possible, while still taking in to account any legitimate needs of law enforcement or measures necessary to restore the security and integrity of our system. Any notification of breach will occur in a private email correspondence with affected members or in a highly visible forum within the Infochimps interface itself.

## Links to Other Websites; Email Referrals

From time to time, Infochimps may include links to third party websites. This does not in any way speak as an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. Infochimps strongly advises our users to be aware of and review any privacy or terms of use made available by these third party sites, as Infochimps has no control over their ability to insert cookies or their collection/solicitation of your personally identifiable information. Any links that are found to link to sites that promote illegal or pornographic activity, however, will be removed. Until Infochimps has an integrated system in place for the reporting of these links, users may send an email with their concerns about any link on our site to [help@infochimps.com](mailto:help@infochimps.com).

If you choose to use any referral function to tell friends about the Service, you will be required to provide your name and email address and the email addresses of your friends. The form automatically sends your friends a one-time email inviting them to visit the Service. Infochimps does not access or store this information, except to send the invitation to visit the Service. By using the referral form you are authorizing us to contact your friends on your behalf and to list your name and email address as the referring party.

## Forums & Other Interactive Services

The Service may include discussion forums or other interactive areas or services, including blogs, chat rooms, bulletin boards, message boards, online hosting or storage services, or other areas or services in which you or third parties create, post or store any content, messages, comments, materials or other items on the Service (“Interactive Areas”). If you use an Interactive Area, you should be aware that these areas are open to the public and any personal information you post or provide at registration may be viewable by others. Infochimps is not responsible for personal information you submit in connection with the Interactive Areas, nor is Infochimps responsible for how others might use that information, including to send you unsolicited messages. Interactive Area postings may be retained indefinitely. If at any time you would like to remove a posting, please send an email to [help@infochimps.com](mailto:help@infochimps.com). Keep in mind that removal of a posting from an Interactive Area does not mean that the posting will be deleted from all systems.

## Non-U.S. Users

The Service is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Service from a jurisdiction with privacy laws or regulations that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Service, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

## Note to California Residents

The State of California enacted the Shine the Light law (CA Civil Code Sec 198.83) that permits customers of Infochimps who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information during the past year for marketing purposes. To make such a request, send an email to [help@infochimps.com](mailto:help@infochimps.com).

## Conditions of Use, Notices and Revisions

By using the Service, you accept that your use and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and the TOS, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of Texas. If you have any concern about privacy issues, please contact us as directed in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies only to Infochimps and not to any third-parties that may be accessed through hyper-links. Infochimps reserves the right to occasionally update this Privacy Policy. At such time, Infochimps will also revise the “last updated” date at the end of the Privacy Policy. Infochimps recommends that you periodically visit this page regularly to review the most current version of this Privacy Policy and monitor any changes.

Last updated: March 25, 2011. © 2009-2013 Infochimps, Inc.
